Zhijiang Wang

0401868849 zhijiang.wang@uqconnect.edu.au Github: https://github.com/zhijiang95?tab=repositories (please check my portfolio and other project in Github)

Introduction

I am currently studying Masters in Interaction Design at the University Of Queensland. Over the past 2 years I have been studying human computer interaction, graphic and web design. These studies have Allowed me to gain proficient skills in both user interface and user experience.

I believe I would be a good fit for the [UI!] team not only because of my extensive knowledge in the field, but also because sustainability is something near and dear to me. I've always wanted to put my abilities toward something that could better our world and an opportunity with [UI!] would allow me to do just that!

Experience

WINTER SCHOLAR; UNIVERSITY OF QUEENSLAND — 06/2020 — PRESENT

My role as winter research scholar is to build a survey website collecting research data and visualise it to users. I'm responsible for both front-end and back-end development. The close working experience with Dr Stylianou and Dr Gomersall enable me to have a clear communication skill to propose my approach and research results.

VOLUNTEER; ROBOGALS; BRISBANE — 07/2019—PRESENT

The main responsibility as a volunteer in Rebogals is to help children build a basic understanding of coding language mechanism.

INTERN; LONG MUSEUM; SHANGHAI — 03/2017—12/2017

My role as in intern gave me good experience in many departments this includes

- Sorting out paperwork and data inputing
- Providing customer service to visiting guests
- Exhibition booking editing

Skills

- · Illustrator, Photoshop, Unity, Nvivo
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, React
- Programming Language(PYTHON, SQL)

Education

Communication University of Zhejiang — Bachelor Choreography (2013 -2017)

University of Queensland, Brisbane, QLD — Masters Interaction Design (2018-Present)